const previousLetter = [
    { question: 'b', answers: ['a'] },
    { question: 'c', answers: ['b'] },
    { question: 'd', answers: ['c'] },
    { question: 'e', answers: ['d'] },
    { question: 'f', answers: ['e'] },
    { question: 'g', answers: ['f'] },
    { question: 'h', answers: ['g'] },
    { question: 'i', answers: ['h'] },
    { question: 'j', answers: ['i'] },
    { question: 'k', answers: ['j'] },
    { question: 'l', answers: ['k'] },
    { question: 'm', answers: ['l'] },
    { question: 'n', answers: ['m'] },
    { question: 'o', answers: ['n'] },
    { question: 'p', answers: ['o'] },
    { question: 'q', answers: ['p'] },
    { question: 'r', answers: ['q'] },
    { question: 's', answers: ['r'] },
    { question: 't', answers: ['s'] },
    { question: 'u', answers: ['t'] },
    { question: 'v', answers: ['u'] },
    { question: 'w', answers: ['v'] },
    { question: 'x', answers: ['w'] },
    { question: 'y', answers: ['x'] },
    { question: 'z', answers: ['y'] },
];

export default previousLetter;
